http://www.codepink4peace.org/privacy_policy

Skip navigation
ACTION ALERT: Low turnout, but free elections in Venezuela are a blow to regime change
ACTION ALERT: CODEPINK Condemns Assassination of Iranian Scientist
Privacy policy
Personal information is collected from supporters, donors, and volunteers for the overall purpose of meeting CODEPINK's mission to end war in Iraq, prevent new wars, and help sustain peace around the world. Prior to collecting personal information, the specific purpose and intended use is documented on all sign-up forms, petitions, and donation pages.
The personal information gathered by CODEPINK is kept in confidence. CODEPINK staff and volunteers are authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered.
E-mail communications
CODEPINK sends frequent information and action alert notices through email. All emails sent include a link to CODEPINK's "unsubscribe" online form, which users may fill out should they wish to have their names removed from the email list.
Website and Secure Donation Handling
Our website is operated for the benefit of the public at large and those interested in supporting our mission. We record visits to our website for statistical research purposes only, without recording the identity of the user. Any personal information collected such as e-mail addresses and financial information, is knowingly and specifically supplied to us by the website user. We contract third party providers to handle some of our on-line activities, including on-line donations. These companies offer secure sites. We select these service providers carefully and take all reasonable precautions to ensure that they protect your personal information. Our online software is routinely updated to maximize protection of such information.
Copyright
All information contained on the site is © CODEPINK. This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution - Noncommercial - Share Alike 3.0 United States License. Any trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
